♪ ♪
>> PROGRAMMING NOTE, NEW PODCAST
COMING OUT HANGING WITH ME,
DROPS TOMORROW FEATURING A CIA
WHISTLE-BLOWER.
HERE'S A SNEAK PEEK.
>>> ALL OF THIS IS WHAT IS
REALLY FASCINATING BECAUSE IF I
HAD TO GO BACK AND PICK OTHER
CAREERS IN MY LIFE, I LOVE WHAT
I'M DOING.
JUST TALKING HE WAS A LOT OF FUN
FOR ME.
AND HANGING OUT WITH YOU AT ALL
OF THE OTHER PEOPLE I GET TO
INTERVIEW AND THE EXPERIENCE I
HAVE HAD, I WOULD NEVER GIVE
THOSE UP.
HOWEVER, IF THERE IS OTHER
THINGS THAT I THINK COULD BE
REALLY COOL, BEING A SPY WOULD
BE RIGHT UP THERE.
>> FRANK LIM SURPRISED THEY
HAVEN'T APPROACHED YOU BECAUSE
OF YOUR --
>> I THINK I HAVE BEEN
APPROACHED.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.